Michelle Masters

Pharmacist - RITE AID PHARMACY

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Michelle-Masters/caefc432fcc3a12c

I am seeking a position as an Outpatient Pharmacist in a hospital environment where I can utilize my passion for patient care and knowledge of medication to assist both doctors and nurses in optimizing drug therapy for patients. With experience in retail pharmacy since 2007, along with my current degree as a pharmacist, I have developed a knowledge base, communication skills, and learned through experience to provide personalized care as well as to be a reliable member of the health care community.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pharmacist

RITE AID PHARMACY - Philadelphia, PA - October 2013 to Present

Efficiently answers multi-line phone and processes high volume of order requests from nurses, doctors and other healthcare providers

- Properly fills and dispenses prescriptions
- Checks prescriptions for appropriate dosage, drug interactions, allergies and or contraindications before dispensing medications
- · Screens and administers vaccinations to appropriate candidates
- Organizes and participates in health care fairs to educate the community on disease states, medications, and services Rite Aid offers
- Evaluates and implements necessary interventions for individual prescriptions through medication therapy management

Pharmacy Intern Summer/Winter

WAL-MART PHARMACY - Rochester, NY - 2010 to December 2012

Received and assisted in dispensing of prescriptions to the patients

- Discussed with medical professionals about prescriptions or medication routines
- Consulted with patients on their prescriptions to achieve optimum patient compliance
- · Assisted the pharmacist with their duties
- Organized health care clinics in several Wal-Mart pharmacies in the Rochester, NY area
- Contributed to conference calls made by the District Pharmacy Manager

Pharmacy Technician

WALGREENS PHARMACY - Rochester, NY - March 2007 to August 2009

Focused on patient interaction and customer service by helping patients on medication use, medication problems, and other various pharmacy tasks

• Expanded upon communication and customer service skills by addressing and solving patient complaints and problems

- Responsible for contacting insurance companies in regards to patients' medications
- Responsible for filling, inputting, greeting, selling, and other technician duties

EDUCATION

Doctor of Pharmacy

MASSACHUSETTS COLLEGE OF PHARMACY AND HEALTH SCIENCES - Boston, MA May 2013

UNIVERSITY AT BUFFALO, THE STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - Buffalo, NY May 2008